K.
And, um, but your salco is different,
right?
What do you mean?
They issued that they were having that
all of them were.
or having with this customer gateway.
Yeah, well,
they're different because they're the
first customer that we're sending
integration to.
Okay.
The first, the first one was all manual,
so it was an easier scenario.
OK, but that the so both are different,
right?
Use one and HyperCare is another one.
Ohh, no, no,
the hyper cares for use out go go live.
Oh, okay, I see. So hypercare is like...
Like the project name or?
It's like another word for support,
I guess. You know,
you go live and you have that dedicated
support available.
Ohh.
Oh yes, of course. The name says it.
HyperCare. Okay. So David,
Yeah.
I have a lot of things again for you.
Awesome.
First things first,
I don't know if we're going to have this
APIR meeting. The other one,
I think they got canceled.
So we're not having that anymore.
I don't know what's going on with that.
I just,
I don't know if you could see it on
Friday, I think.
I send it the complete analysis,
cross-customer analysis of the gateways.
Yes, I saw that.
I also made an HTML,
so it's easier to read that in an Excel
file. I'll let you know your text on that.
Is that accurate, or am I like,
since I didn't get a lot of feedback
because everyone...
were very occupied and other things.
I couldn't get like...
All the things that I needed.
Yeah, I...
I looked at it. It looks helpful,
but I'm not the primary audience for that.
So I think we want to get Thomas and
Devin's input on that.
Okay.
It does look good.
And then based on their input,
and the other thing I really need to
understand is the details of what went
Hmm.
wrong with you, Salco,
because that's where we need to see how
Mm.
we can use what you did to avoid that the
next time.
Exactly.
That's what I want to know as well.
Yeah,
so I've been trying not to ask my
But basically, just...
questions until they're available,
but we're going to have a debrief for
this hypercare.
Okay,
but do you think it was okay to send it,
complete it Friday? I was feeling like...
We were taking like too long to,
so I just decided to send it anyways.
No, that's fine. I think that's right.
Yeah.
Because I...
So I don't know if you checked it.
This is the summary,
the complete summary of it.
But basically what it says here,
these are all the points that my findings
list, let's say, in this analysis.
And but basically they say like some
customers have this.
behavior,
some other customers said this behavior,
and it actually tells me how things were
put together on each gateway as well.
For example,
here it detected that some of them were
already being wired to Boomi.
But not completely.
And I...
And some of them have some shared like
logic on that.
But that's pretty much it,
like the things that they were expecting,
right?
Some of it,
I don't know if there's a level deeper we
I don't know.
can go with it.
Mm.
Yeah, okay.
Hi, Smith. Let me work with Steve.
I know there's a couple questions that we
had for the Gateway team.
And their response was basically that
they'll...
They won't be able to tell us that
information until we do,
until we're ready for that customer.
Because it was too much to dig into each
single customer and give us a response of
how each one of them is using the gateway.
Mm.
But if I give you those specific,
specific questions, then maybe...
Yeah, but we have...
That'll give you an idea of some of what
we need.
Okay. But that was the main point, right?
Nirab last time told you that we don't
have time for that,
for asking each one because it takes a
long time. So we should use their code.
We should use their code to analyze
Exactly.
what's going on and take action.
Mhm.
That's enough, I think.
I just need to understand.
Because I get confused,
I try to read this and it's so weird.
I am learning a lot,
but this is difficult.
Yeah.
Let's go to the next one.
So let me show you, just so you know.
So,
the project now is not named Shipments,
it's named Odyssey One Stage,
Odyssey One Stage, basically.
Because we were all going to have all of
them, right?
And, for example,
here I already have home, but it's empty.
I need to start working on that in orders
and carriers and shipments. Well,
it's pretty much done and all of that.
So yeah, as you can see,
it's it's getting it's getting it's
getting alive.
I am hosting this in this place,
which is Vercel.
And.
So why I'm doing this?
Because Thomas didn't actually provide me
a solution for the link, right?
I know Thomas provided me a place to host
Mhm.
this thing.
Yeah.
But it doesn't matter because still I in
that host that IT provided me,
I still need to do the...
The the port forwarding, anyway, so...
It's basically like the same thing. Yeah,
we don't have like...
Okay.
This is better because it's now live.
I don't need to run in my computer.
It's working good,
and we have a decent link,
so it's readable.
Um...
And I wanted to like confirm, ohh,
one other thing is that I make Figma
connect to Cloud already, so...
Oh, awesome.
all of the components of, for example,
I am trying to work on the sidebar first,
right, piece by piece.
So all of the components are synchronized
Mm.
with the project.
So everything you're going to see here is
going to come from here.
And every time we do change here,
it will reflect it.
That's awesome. OK.
Yes.
So, that's something, for example,
Congnizant doesn't have,
because to them it's just like eyeballing
the PDFs or something,
so that's one strategy.
When I'm done with this,
I'm gonna start doing the orders and the
tracking and the other ones, and why?
Because...
Those are using, I know they are using.
These components,
but they are drifting from each other
because rush life comes hard and we
Efrain had to rush on some things and
they are not looking the same,
so this will be like later,
this will be the...
Um...
like the source of truth for everything.
Right now,
it will be the source of truth for
homepage and then for carriers and for
OK, great.
shipments as well. Okay?
It's like my living here.
It's inside here. You see?
Mhm.
So, it's normal equipment, nothing,
nothing different,
nothing outside of Odyssey.
Um, I just need to...
Help me with something I need to
understand.
I am recording this call so I can have
something in relationship.
for of each domain,
so I understand the relationship between
them. Could you like, I can give you,
I can start a conversation on this and
then you will tell me like,
is that okay or if you want to add
something else, okay?
Okay.
So, first is the homepage.
From the homepage, you want to have,
we'll say you want to have dashboard,
you want to have...
And those, what is it called?
Widgets.
Mhm.
Okay.
Then,
this is where it becomes complicated.
I need to understand the relationship
between orders, carriers, shipments,
and also tracking. So far,
I understand that you have different...
Like, for example,
shipment have a has an order and inside
that order you have different products,
etcetera, but...
As of now, my mind says, okay,
whenever I create an order.
It's creating a shipment as well, right?
Mmh.
That's correct.
Yes.
So, whenever it is created,
that is automatically tendered as well.
It can be automatically tendered, yes.
Okay, so, yeah.
That is good. And what about carriers?
When is this?
Is this the place that we are going to
list the carriers?
Yeah,
that's more like a master data screen
And.
that'll show carriers and compliance for
the carriers,
what they're qualified to do.
Okay.
Okay,
but the user is going to be able to add
carriers or not?
Yep.
Okay, so carriers can be manually added.
And also we have a database with carriers
Yes, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
already, right?
Right.
And orders,
and whenever we create an order,
those are all actually listed in the
database as well, right?
Mhm.
Yeah.
And oh, let's go back to this one first.
So we have homepage.
The homepage is dedicated to each user.
That's what I understood so far.
So each user will be able to access the
different customers for the homepage.
For example, Efrain recently thought that
the homepage will be empty in the
beginning.
So each user should be able to create its
own,
like put its own widgets and everything.
But you're going to have a...
Pre-defined by all this thing, right?
I think we would want to predefine one.
Yeah.
You're gonna have this.
Okay,
so let's say I am one of those users
which was planners, right?
So let's say I got hired as a planner in
Mhm.
Odyssey.
they are going to give me this platform
to start working.
So whenever I got my credential,
I start here. Let's say I am Amy.
I am gonna see already this populated,
right?
Mhm.
Because they are going to be assigning,
assign me,
they're going to be assigning me a
certain amount of...
of customers, right?
Yep.
Okay.
How many customers does each user
normally has?
I believe that the operations level has
three to four.
Yeah.
And their managers have 8 to 12.
Okay.
So, planners are operations, right?
Yep.
Basically.
Yeah, yeah,
so the planner planners have three to
Ohh.
four, and then um,
the plan the managers have 8 to 12.
Okay.
What does managers, as a general,
you don't need to be super specific,
but what can a manager can do,
what that a normal planner or operations
can't do normally?
I don't think there's any limit. Yeah,
I don't think there's any limitation
Within Odyssey one.
right now.
Okay.
So managers are more for like assigning
planners each.
Let's say.
Yeah, yeah.
And they might have a client they work on
Okay.
too,
but they want to see all of their team's
customers.
So both are going to do the same job as
well, right? Of planning the thing. Okay.
Yeah.
Uh, let's go to the next one.
And so would you say this is true?
Like first we start with home?
Then we start with creating an order and
then we should see carriers or shipments.
Shipments.
I am.
Okay,
and carriers is more like an overview,
or is something that is dependent as
orders,
because orders needs to be first in the
flow, right? Always.
The orders and shipments are in tracking
is transactional,
and carrier and customer are more master
data.
Oh, okay.
Area and customer. OK,
customer is in is the next thing then,
Mhm.
right? We're gonna have a customer.
Yeah, that'll be, yeah.
Mm.
Okay,
so like would you say the data that is
shared between orders, shipments,
and tracking is going to be...
Taking, or no, that is different.
You could, you could,
you could say that orders,
let's say shipments, orders,
and tracking will take the data from
carriers, right?
Yeah,
it'll it'll foreign key into a carrier,
but...
The team that uses carrier will be using
it for something different than shipments
and orders and tracking.
Okay, so you have different users,
but what I meant is is
Yes.
The platform will use these carriers,
right? For example,
Mhm.
whenever I create an order,
I will assign a carrier or it will be
tendered to a carrier from this list,
right? Okay.
Raedt.
Yep.
Okay, that's good.
And then tracking is consuming the same
information from the other two.
Okay,
that's I think that's that's what I
wanted to know so far regarding this,
share this the new link. Well,
Okay.
the other link works as well,
but this is more.
Um...
Where are you?
There you go.
What else? Do you have anything for me?
I don't think so. No,
I did reach out to John about reviewing
the shipment data feedback internally.
I just want to make sure we don't start
building without.
consolidating everything,
making sure there's nothing conflicting,
and making sure that we agree with the
feedback.
Mm.
Okay, sure.
Because if we don't agree with it and
it's only from one person,
we want to make sure the rest of the team
is aligned with that as well.
Yeah, of course.
I totally agree with that. If you want,
I can join you in your meetings.
But anyways,
I was giving a look and also I'm not
going to start anything before we have
Okay, yeah,
John has said he'll schedule it.
discussed about it.
Okay, yeah,
Jonas said it'll schedule tomorrow or
Friday, and I'm sure he'll bring you in.
Okay, that's great. That's super nice.
Do we have a rush on that? Not.
Well, I mean, yeah, there's,
we want to try and keep the business
moving on this, I think,
because we don't want to hold up the
No.
development. I think separately,
I have to escalate to the business to be
a little more prompt on their feedback
and coordinated.
Yeah, and you know what I noticed?
They didn't, like, Timothy most team,
they didn't bring great feedback.
It was more like one point and that's it.
And I was, why?
Right, and some of it wasn't real. Yeah,
yeah.
Why only one thing?
And some of it was just demo feedback.
It wasn't like actual development
feedback.
Mm.
You know what I mean?
Yes, of course.
Like, it's a prototype,
so like the data isn't going to be
perfect.
Oh, but it looks like a demo, right?
That's the that's the thing.
Oh, yes, it does look like a demo.
I'm referring specifically to where they
said it was tendered,
but there was no tender history, right?
Of course.
Like small things like that that aren't,
yeah.
Like that.
Okay, so on my side,
I'm trying to have as close as possible,
the data as close as possible as reality.
Obviously,
I'm not going to put the real data,
but I'm trying to put it as close as
Mmh.
possible.
We don't have these confusions as well
and it looks like I'm ready.
But one other thing is...
Yeah.
What do you think about this? What's your.
..
How do you see this in the long run?
Because right now,
I feel we're going to be done with this
real quickly.
Once I get past the part of components,
which is like the very,
like the most difficult one, let's say.
But later,
we will so we will have this other domain
super fast.
I would like this to be more than just a
demo, just a, let's say, not a demo.
I would like this to be more like just...
Um...
Was it called was prototype right?
Mhm.
Because it is as valuable as a
development thing. As you know,
we have very synchronized components
between Figma here.
So this will look much better than what
Congnizant is doing.
This is what I, I'm trying to like, um...
advise you before when we start doing
this. But I'd like to know from your side,
what do you think about this? Is this a...
The and this, in a way,
will detach us from from Congnizant,
you know, if we, if, if like things align.
Yeah,
so you are you referring to like you
doing the front end and handing it off to
them instead of just the UX design?
At least we need to hand this as a
documentation,
so they can use this instead of having
Mangesh to write the user stories to see
how it looks, everything,
every little detail. And also, yes,
Mhm.
this is not like to attribute myself.
But it's the reality. This is already a...
It's not like a mock-up,
it's really taking the shape of a real
Okay.
application.
It will be a waste of accomplishments to
just give it as a visual design.
As I told you,
Mhm.
I had a little experience with
Kathleen,
I tried to hand all hand net native team
a component instead of just a visual
design in Figma,
because that way they don't get things
messed up and they and they didn't like
there was resistance, right?
Yeah.
But what do you think?
I need to know your opinion on this.
I definitely want to do that with
Congnizant.
And I'll talk to Nirab about Irina side
of it,
because I know they're a little bit
reluctant, but Congnizant,
which should be easier to do that with.
Okay. Yes,
the idea is to hand this over to the
front-end team, for example.
They will have to review it.
Instead of developing thing by thing,
they can review it just like a code
Mhm.
review and hand it over to the
The backend team, for example, right? So,
they start because the only thing that
Okay.
this will not have is the backend part,
yeah, and the business logic, let's say,
but as far as the front end,
it will be already done and it will look
Yeah.
much better and we don't have to fight
with the developers team later.
to do redundant work, you know.
Yeah, exactly.
That's okay, okay, I'm glad.
Okay, yeah, I'm fully on board.
I just need to see what the politics
behind making that happen.
Yes, of course.
And I didn't want to respond to Kathleen
in the last call either, too directly,
because, you know,
Priya was in the call or other Congnizant
people. So I don't know how.
I don't want to mess up my words.
Right, okay.
Yeah, I'll take care of that.
Just.
Okay, that's it, I think.
I, I know I have something else.
Awesome. They have it.
but I don't remember.
I will call you later.
All right, well, you know where to get me.
Okay.
Cool, very good. Yeah,
and I did tell Nirab about how you're
Okay, David.
doing the whole front end and he was
impressed.
So I know he's going to support it.
I just we just need to figure out the
Yeah.
steps to put that in place.
Yeah, exactly.
One thing I need to mention is that now
developer teams are working with
something called Dev spec-driven
development. How does that work?
Let me show you real quick.
Mhm.
It's because it's super interesting.
Yeah,
I'm writing that down so I can research
that.
Yeah, spec-driven development,
that is a new trend that big companies
are using.
I actually took a lot of hours in
starting that in a course from an AI
engineer from Spain that is
So.
How does this work?
It's like this is super simple,
so let's do one more.
So, this is the idea,
this is the stakeholder.
And this is game management.
Which is your?
And this is the,
maybe this is alongside is the UX.
Yeah.
And this is the Devin.
Yeah.
So.
Yeah.
Whenever the stakeholders need something,
it's responsible responsibility of the
manager.
To do the discovery, right? So,
here is the discovery part,
and he does it with the help of the UX,
so...
Because why?
Because you need visuals to understand.
how things work, right?
And once this is done,
Mhm.
he prepares the JIRA,
the stories and everything,
and they give it to devs, right?
And in this part,
Yep.
we can have like different flows as well,
like we can tell each other,
but the idea is to have this as clear as
possible so we don't have to.
to loop this thing around too much
because we waste energy.
For the spec driven development,
things change a lot because you have a
stakeholder that is unchanged.
We have management.
And we have death.
And.
Oh, we have the UX here.
I should copy that one. OK.
Ohh.
So brings the information brings from the
stakeholder management does a much bigger.
This is the AI part, right?
And this is UX.
So...
The UX makes the prototype in here with
AI.
Right.
Mm.
This is so far what we were doing.
This goes like this and just goes like
this.
And because of the prototype, you go,
or you use the prototype to say to say
that the stakeholder, hey,
this is the feedback and give me another
feedback. OK, that's it.
Once this is done,
instead of creating a JIRA.
Because here I forgot to put the Jira.
Yeah.
Instead of creating the Jira,
you create here the empty files,
which could be in Jira as well.
Why?
Because devs also use AI, right?
Mhm.
But they don't read it anymore directly
from the JIRA.
They have a broad understanding,
but they make their AI agents read from
this empty files that you are providing
it. So initially,
my intention with the notebook that
By the way, we need to fix that part up,
because I don't have it yet either.
Is that the deal with Notebook is that we
can collect all of this information in
Okay.
Notebook, right?
And Notebook will give us...
Mmh.
These empty files.
Raedt.
And notebooks will give us these empty
files, so they are, we are clear to do so.
Ohh.
Once we have this in the files,
we can upload it to GitHub,
we can upload it to Jira, whatever.
But the devs are no longer going to have
to interpret those very specifically.
They need to interpret those broadly.
And their AIs will actually read it and
start developing with it. Right?
Right now.
Mhm.
Right now, for us,
it's a little bit different because since
I know about front-end,
I am making the prototype already
front-end.
It's working as a front-end business,
not just a mock-up. Normally,
this will be a mock-up.
And so, we can use this as a...
Documentation part, so...
to the dev team as well and or as a
deliverable actually.
So the AI of the team,
the dev team will be.
Like,
don't have to lift the weight of the of
the UI/UX part, you know.
Yep.
That's the idea.
So the spec driven development,
instead of creating just the stories,
what it creates is...
Doris.
Then, if from those stories,
you start uh getting um...
specs and from those you start getting
tasks.
And one behind it is the PRD, let's say.
Okay, so you have the PRD,
then you grow mate with a stakeholder,
which with whoever,
and you create the stories,
and from the stories,
which is also AI driven,
the stories start to create the specs,
and from the specs is...
We are splitting the specs more to give
it tasks, to give specific tasks.
So the De is no longer the guy that is
executing each task,
like reading from a list.
The De is actually a management.
as well. So he's only managing this task,
you know?
So he's like overviewing everything.
And he's like deploying sub-agents to
Mhm.
tackle this task.
And he knows which ones are blockers,
which ones are not, etc.
This is the way I am already doing the
prototype. For example,
my PRDs are all of these transcripts that
I have from the meetings.
Then I start to create my own stories.
I don't know if you saw the videos that I
sent you,
that I was sending Jan and you a while
ago.
Ohh.
Well, it was a list of a big list of...
Stories, and from that stories,
my cloud is actually taking creating the
specs,
so on each step I am like Manuela here is
is.
is taking a look at everything is being
done according to plan.
So it's not like automatic.
You have to overview every single step.
So because AI sometimes drifts and
sometimes emits some stuff and stuff like
that. And
But this is basically the flow that it
should be taking.
Most of the time in normal development
teams that they don't use AI,
they don't do this part.
They don't do the specs,
they don't do the tasks.
They just read the stories.
But this...
But when you do that,
you take a lot of ambiguity, right?
Mhm.
And this is where it starts to we start
to have problems,
issues with implementation,
because it's not complete,
because it's not filling the criteria,
because we...
we realized, oh,
something else is missing, you know. Why?
Because this part is very like...
Writing heavy, you need to do,
you need to have a lot of time to do this
manually,
and no teams usually do does this.
Maybe the some scrum masters start does
this part in the industry,
but it's very broad, yeah, but we.
Okay.
With AI, we fix this part.
AI is very good at doing this because
it's basically text, right?
So we have very precise execution of what
Mhm.
is this button should be doing,
what is this button color and all that
stuff. But taking a look, just...
Search for spec-driven development.
And...
And you will understand that better. Also,
let me show you how LinkedIn here in my
Okay.
LinkedIn.
about management as well. Because yeah,
I feel things are changing very fast and
it will be a good idea to do.
To do all of this.
I agree, that looks awesome.
I want to learn more about it, but yeah,
I like the direction.
Yeah, it's...
It's great. I mean,
I really want to do it because I feel
like I'm learning stuff, you know,
not repeating stuff.
Okay, I will send you the links later.
I cannot copy it on my account.
Okay,
is it the one that you reposted 2 weeks
ago? I can see that.
Which one?
The best PM tool.
Efrain.
Yeah, exactly. And basically,
that is that is what we are doing right
Okay.
now. In some ways, you can read it.
It's super good.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Alright, I appreciate that.
Okay.
I'll.
No problem,
we can keep talking about this.
Okay, I'll schedule time with you,
Laurie and I, for notebook as well.
Mm.
Maybe she can show us what she's doing
and see if it triggers anything.
Yeah.
Yeah,
we will see what's going on with that.
Okay.
Okay, awesome. All right, thanks, Manuela.
Thank you.